savingshighway.com 2013-10-01

# Privacy Policy

Information is collected on this website by SavingsHighway, Inc. doing business as SavingsHighway.com, LLC. ("SavingsHighway" or "SH"). SavingsHighway is committed to protecting your privacy and will use your personal information responsibly. Please read below for detailed information about our privacy policy.

Information Collection and Use  
SavingsHighway.com (SH) is the owner of all information collected at this site. We will not share or rent this personal information with or to anyone else in any way that is different from what is disclosed to you in this policy. We may collect information from several different points on our website or the websites of SavingsHighway Independent Member Representatives (IMRs), when you make a purchase from one of our IMRs or have other interactions where personal data is provided.

At certain points in interactive communication with us, you might provide us with personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address. Demographic personal information such as income level, gender, and other personal information of yours may be provided by you on an optional basis.

We may also gather online information regarding your purchases and shopping activities on websites we host (such as those of SavingsHighway IMRs) to improve the content, ease of use and shopping experience on those websites and to improve our marketing and promotions for our company overall and the websites in particular.

In addition, our web server may automatically collect the following non-personally identifiable information:

    * your Internet service provider's address,  
    * the referring URL and  
    * the information on the pages you access on our site or on the sites of the SavingsHighway IMRs since we host those websites.

Personal information that you provide to SavingsHighway will be used by us for the purposes of enabling a SavingsHighway IMR or other SavingsHighway Member or Independent Contractor contact you at your request for the purposes of your becoming a SavingsHighway member, customer or IMR. SavingsHighway may also use your personal information to contact you to keep you informed of developments or opportunities in relation to SavingsHighway, or any of its products or services.

We may also use information collected when you make a purchase on line through a IMR Website or at a SavingsHighway show in order to process your order or purchase, process credit card payments, provide warranty service or advise you of promotions and SavingsHighway product news. We may also send you emails with offers from marketing partners which have products or service we believe might be of interest to you.

We do use third party companies to gather information and provide services to us, for example in maintaining and organizing customer information and conducting promotions, upgrading our Internet services, sending communications and contacting our customers. Some of those third parties will and do have access to the information which customers, members and IMRs provide, including email addresses and credit card information and they may also use cookies on behalf of SavingsHighway.

We may also use third party providers to provide ads for SavingsHighway products or services throughout the Internet. They may provide anonymous information regarding your visits to a SavingsHighway website (or that of a SavingsHighway IMR) and your interaction with the goods and services which SavingsHighway provides. They may also use information about your visits to SavingsHighway and other web sites to target advertisements for goods or services. Your anonymous information is collected through a pixel tab, a standard technology used at most major consumer websites. This technology does not require the use or collection of any personally identifiable information such as your name or email address.

If you have any concerns regarding the use of your information or wish to be removed from our e-mail list, please contact us through our free online help desk at www.savingshighway.com/support.

Children  
We do not intend to collect any personal information from children under the age of eighteen. If a parent or guardian of a child who has provided us with such personal information would like the information deleted from our records, he or she should contact us through our free online help desk at www.savingshighway.com/support. We will then delete the child's personal information from our files.

If we become aware that personally identifiable information regarding a child under the age of 13 has been collected at the Site, we will use such information for the sole purpose of contacting a parent or guardian of the child to obtain verifiable parental consent. If we cannot obtain consent after a reasonable period of time, or if when contacted a parent or guardian requests that we do not use or maintain such information, we will make reasonable efforts to delete it from our records. Upon request by a parent or guardian, SavingsHighway will provide a description of the specific types of personal information collected from a child who is under the age of 13.

Cookies and IP Addresses  
A cookie is a piece of information stored in your hard drive containing information about you. SavingsHighway may place cookies on your hard drive to assist in site navigation and to personalize your experience on the SavingsHighway.com website. If you want to disable those cookies, most Internet browsers will allow you to delete cookies from your computer hard drive, prevent them from being stored, or signal a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions. If you elect to block cookies, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of the features and functions of the SavingsHighway.com website.

We may use a vendor's services to help SavingsHighway measure the effectiveness of advertising and to learn about how visitors to our websites use them. To obtain accurate measurements we may use web beacons and cookies provided by a vendor on our websites. The type of information we would collect would include the specific website and pages visited, and information about transactions made. We may use such data to conduct targeted marketing programs or to determine the nature of our customers and the types of products which each customer finds most attractive.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic data and to recognize customer traffic patterns and site usage.

Links to other Websites  
From time to time SavingsHighway may have a link to other websites of marketing partners or for your convenience. Please check the privacy policies of such other websites which may vary from this one.

We have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content, actions or policies of third party web sites. The inclusion of third party web sites on our Site in no way constitutes an endorsement of such web sites' content, actions or policies.  
Surveys and Contests

The SavingsHighway website may request personal information from you via an electronic entry form for purpose of your participation in sweepstakes, contests or surveys. If you choose to provide the personal information requested, we will use that personal information to administer your participation in the relevant sweepstake, contest or survey and in the other ways indicated in this Privacy Policy.

Right to access and change information  
You have the right to access, review and change any personal information that we might retain. To access or change personal information, please do so from your SavingsHighway.com Members Area BackOffice online or contact us through our online help desk at www.savingshighway.com/support.

Security  
SavingsHighway has adopted reasonable technical and organizational security measures to prevent unauthorized or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction of your personal information. Not all personal information collected on this website will be retained. If you have any concerns regarding the use of your information, contact us through our online help desk at www.savingshighway.com/support.   If you wish to have your email removed from our email list, you can do so at the bottom of our emails or by contacting us through our online help desk at www.savingshighway.com/support.

Changes in Privacy Policy  
We will post any changes to our privacy policy on the relevant section of our website when our policy changes. However, your consent to provision of information under the current policy will be assumed to constitute consent to any new policy. By your continued use of this website we will make the assumption that you have consented to providing personal information under this privacy policy.

Contacting Us  
Please contact us with any questions about our privacy practices, this privacy policy or the protection of your personal information through our online help desk at www.savingshighway.com/support.
